Tanvi Sac<u>hdeva</u>

Senior Frontend/ Full Stack

Contact

Address

Pune, India, 411057

Phone

916 858 8710

E-mail

sachdevatanvi2311@gmail.c

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sachdevatanvi2311/

www

https://tanvisachdeva.githu b.io/tanviprofile.html

Certifications

2021-05

AZ-900 Microsoft Certified
Azure Fundamentals

2021-06

AZ-104 Microsoft Certified Azure Administrator

Skills

Javascript

React

Angular

Typescript

8+ years of experience in Frontend and Fullstack working in multi products of different domains like aerospace, healthcare and telecom. Tech stack - React, Javascript, Typescript, Angular, .NET, C#, REST WEBAPI, HTML, SASS, CSS, Agile and Cloud, Azure certified, OOPS. Have international experience of working in France with Airbus. I am Proactive, Self-directed, Solution oriented and Result driven, experience in leading and managing project delivery with significant experience as an individual contributor.

Work History

2022-04 -Current

Associate Manager (Frontend Lead)

Accenture

- Client: International healthcare client
- React 18, Google cloud, Redux, SCSS, Balsamiq,
 Typescript, React bootstrap, ReactJS, Swagger, GIT,
 Adobe XD, Scrum, Http, Agile
- Develop healthcare application from scratch, gather requirements, involved in mock-up meetings and coding these into real time UI following all technology standards and delivering quality code.
- Strong attention to detail and understanding of UI concepts to provide perspective on front and backend technologies and their overall impact on the creative process.
- Effectively manage scope and client expectations on individual assignments.
- Work with an Agile team to deliver applications iteratively, and incorporate feedback into future iterations.

2019-06 -2022-04

Technical Lead

Sopra Steria India

- Client European multinational aerospace leader
- Angular, Javascript, Typescript, .NET REST Webapi, C#, Agile, GIT, IIS, Mongodb
- Lead and performed end to end delivery of web applications starting from requirement understanding to implementation to deployment.
 Contribute to the end-to-end codebase of an application including rich frontend, thoughtful web

REST WEBAPI

.NET Full Stack

Scrum

Agile

C#

Leadership and Management

Azure

HTML

CSS

Mongodb

Cloud

Programming

Object-Oriented programming

Algorithms

APIs, and well-designed databases.

- Participate in all scrum ceremonies. Involved in scoping and estimation of user stories during PI planning, with Product owners/client/business.
- Mentored Web Application development team members who are on a technical career path and are interested in becoming future technical leads and engineers.

2018-06 -2019-06

Lead Engineer

HCL Technologies Ltd.

- Client American multinational technology leader
- ASP.net MVC, GIT, Azure, jQuery, Ajax, JavaScript, CSS, C#
- Investigating bugs in software application based on technical expertise and developing solutions in accordance with quality accredited standards (W3C and accessibility guidelines).
- Mentored team members on technical front so that quality code is delivered with minimal postproduction bugs/issues.

2015-08 -2018-04

Product Integration Engineer

EdgeVerve Systems Ltd.

- Client American multinational telecom leader
- Jauery, Javascript, Angular, C#.NET MVC, SQL
- Analyze business problems, develop technology solutions to those problems and manage project through its lifecycle.
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions. Providing timely deliverables to client, solving post production bugs/issues were handled.

2014-09 -2015-07

Systems Engineer

Infosys Ltd.

Education

2010-08 -2014-07

B.Tech: Computer Science And Engineering

Rajasthan Technical University